Hey guys, have you ever heard of Mr. Nice Guy Talk?
What? You don't know much about it?
That's a pussy!
What! I want more people to know about TALK!
Sshh shh shh shh!
But, but, but! Don't worry!
You'll like her even more when you see this Yakanto Idol!
Yakanto Idol!
Ki lak oko.
Ki-Ki-Raq-Oko.
Ki-Ki-Ra-Ku-Ku-Oko.
What's that?
Kiki means airaku.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
That's the kettle on the kettle.
No, no, no, no, no.
I have a member.
I like Mr. Tork the best. He's the type I can live with.
Members? They're all very kind.
They're all kind.
I'm thinking of becoming a craftsman when I'm no more questions.
It's the only way to be an idol.
Idols?
There is no other way.
Yakanto-idol!
Here we are!
I'm Stardust's cute-histress Yakanto!
Thank you very much!
Let's call today's guest!
Yes! Stardust of Ujiranmijinokunoku!
Tachibana Karen Dacha from Ikinari Talk!
Please give my best regards to her!
Please give my best regards!
Please take care of them!
I see you're out, sorry for the wait for your voice.
I'm sorry!
I heard your voice before I called you.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure?
Thank you very much!
Tachibana-san, you were the Cinderella of the 2nd Staplerfest.
I think the 3rd Staplerfest was Mr. Tao Yoshida.
That's right.
He's the co-host of the festival, right?
I gave him instructions.
What do you think about the 3rd Staplerfest again?
I know it's been a little while, but we've done two Stapler Festivals.
Yes, the second one...
I wanted to do something for Mr. Tayu, even if it was just a little.
I tried my best and was chosen as Cinderella.
But I had always thought of Cinderella as a group shot.
I always thought that I was Cinderella.
I had some resistance to the idea that I was Cinderella.
This was the third time I was able to shoot Cinderella in a group.
It was very good that suddenly I could say proudly that Tayu was Cinderella.
I see... there was some resistance the first time.
Yes, I had a strong feeling that we all fought together to make this film.
But it was very moving.
The faces of the members...
This is Tayu and his wife.
And the frustrated face of manager Fuji.
Fuji manager's face.
He was a wonderful host.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy...
I'm sorry, I'm just going to advertise it here.
The Blu-ray will be on sale until 23:59 on May 7th.
The Blu-ray will be on sale until 23:59.
I'm sure you'll be able to see the video of the event, and I'm sure you'll be able to see me as the host.
And Mr. Michimoto is currently on a nationwide tour.
Thank you very much.
How do you feel when you look back on the past?
Well, this tour is a little different from the previous ones.
In the past, we tended to push through with a lot of power.
In the past, we tended to push through with power or convey our energy to the maximum extent.
That's the image I had.
This time, there are some parts that show a little more.
It's a tour called "Never Lose, Never Lose, Never Lose, Never Lose".
It's different from the other tours, so it's like a set where you don't lose.
So please don't lose to yourself.So don't beat yourself up.
It's not a weather turnaround.
at ease
I'm taking it easy
Rhythm
Rhythm.
Easy-going.
I don't know.
It's right on.
That's the direction.
I feel like I'm trying to express that.
I think I can show you a lot of different kinds of talk.
I'm doing my best.
There's some carefree optimism in it.
It's a little too much fun.
That's it!
That's the kettle.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
He was pushed aside by force.
I wondered what you were talking about for a moment.
He's expressing his love for you.
By all means.
If you weren't interested at the time...
I couldn't hear the idol's name any more.
That's how I feel.
This show is called
Kamakura-chan
Mr. Nakajima
Daisho-san
Mr. Ren
Yanen-san.
Thank you for all your support!
I look forward to seeing you again!